# Tharindu Nadeeshan

Swansea, Wales, United Kingdom



hpatnadeeshan@gmail.com



+447498520828



linkedin.com/in/tharindu-nadeeshan

### Summary

As a civil engineer with four years of experience, I'm currently pursuing a full stack web development course at Code Institute in the UK to pivot my career into software development. My strong problem-solving and analytical skills, combined with my passion for learning new programming languages and technologies, make me an ideal candidate for software development roles. With my unique perspective gained from my background in civil engineering, I'm confident in my ability to contribute to any team and add value to projects. Let's connect and explore how I can help your organization!

### **Experience**



### Civil Engineer

Road Development Authority Oct 2021 - Sep 2022 (1 year)



#### 🔼 Civil Engineer

State Development & Construction Corporation of Sri Lanka Feb 2021 - Sep 2021 (8 months)

## Planning Engineer

Gamini Construction Sep 2020 - Jan 2021 (5 months)

### \* Civil Engineer

Maga Engineering (Private) Limited Feb 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year 8 months)

# Engineer Intern

Central Engineering Consultancy Bureau Jul 2017 - Oct 2017 (4 months)

#### **Education**



#### 🕥 Code Institute

Diploma Level 5, Web Development Feb 2023 - Mar 2024 Learning front end development - HTML, CSS & Java script back end- Python



## University of Moratuwa

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Civil Engineering 2014 - 2018



# Java Institute for Advanced Technology

Computer Software Engineering 2013 - 2014



### Richmond College

1998 - 2012

### **Skills**

Programming • Web Development • HTML5 • HTML • Python (Programming Language) • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Setting out • Project Planning • 3D Modeling Software